myleadconsultant.com 2015-04-07

# MyLeadConsultant | Data & Privacy Policy

MyLeadConsultant.com collects e-mail addresses of people who send us e-mail and/or subscribe to our newsletters. We also collect information on what pages users access and information provided to us by users via surveys and site registrations. Such information may contain personal data about you including your address, phone numbers, credit card numbers etc. MyLeadConsultant protects credit card information according to Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI-DSS). We are not allowed to disclose such personal information without your written permission. However, certain information collected from you and about you is used within the context of providing our services to you. The information we collect is not shared with, sold or rented to others except under certain circumstances and which your use of the Service is deemed to provide to us a valid consent to disclose the following:

  1. MyLeadConsultant may share personal information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MyLeadConsultant’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

## What we do with your information

  1. The term “Personal Information” as used herein is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate the person to whom such information pertains. The Personal Information that we collect will be subject to this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time.
  2. When you register for MyLeadConsultant we ask for your name, company name, email address, billing address, credit card information. Members who sign up for the free account are not required to enter a credit card however if you want to enable your account for upgrades, you will need to provide your credit card information.
  3. MyLeadConsultant uses the information we collect for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

**Plain English:** When you sign up you provide personal information which we collect and use. For the check-out process we also collect your credit card information.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information, such as credit card number on our registration form, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Credit card details are stored and encrypted with out "Processing" merchant services. We DO NOT Store this information on our servers at all - we actually do not even see your payment methods. As a level 1 PCI-DSS compliant service provider we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at support@MyLeadConsultant.com.

**Plain English:** We will encrypt your credit card and sensitive information at industry standards. Because stuff happens, we can’t guarantee 100% security of your data. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Every computer that accesses our website is assigned a different cookie by us.

Which means,

To identify you electronically, a cookie will be stored on your computer. We have a “remarketing” tool running that allows us to take note of your visits to our site and show you relevant ads on our website and across the Internet. You can always opt out.

### Google Analytics, Facebook and Remarketing

We use a service provided by Google called Google Analytics (GA). GA permits us to reach people who have previously visited our site, and show them relevant advertisements when they visit other sites across the Internet in the Google Display Network. This is often called ‘remarketing’.

Cookies can be used to track your session on our website, to serve customized ads from Google and other third party vendors. When you visit this website, you may view advertisements posted on the site by Google or other third parties. Through first-party and third party cookies, these third parties may collect information about you while you are visiting this website and other websites. They may use this data to show you advertisements on this website and across the Internet based on your prior visits to this website and elsewhere on the Internet. We do not collect this information or control the content of the advertisements that you will see.

### Opting Out

You may be able to opt out of customized Google Display Network ads by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager (<http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>), and the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on (<http://www.google.ca/ads/preferences/plugin/>).

Your use of this website without opting out means that you understand and agree to data collection to provide you with remarketing ads using GA and cookies from other third party vendors based on your prior visits to this website and elsewhere on the Internet.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our homepage so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Which means, We may change this Privacy Statement. If it’s a big change, we will inform you, right here.
